<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>搜索 on 淡淡博客 – 记录生活点滴，关注Python数据挖掘、深度学习相关技术</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/tags/%E6%90%9C%E7%B4%A2/</link><description>Recent content in 搜索 on 淡淡博客 – 记录生活点滴，关注Python数据挖掘、深度学习相关技术</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.i-ll.cc/tags/%E6%90%9C%E7%B4%A2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HDU 1010 - Tempter of the Bone（DFS 奇偶剪枝）</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/55/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/55/</guid><description>Description The doggie found a bone in an ancient maze, which fascinated him a lot. However, when he picked it up, the maze began to shake, and the doggie could feel the ground sinking. He realized that the bone was a trap, and he tried desperately to get out of this maze. The maze was a rectangle with sizes N by M. There was a door in the maze. At</description></item><item><title>HDU 1016 - Prime Ring Problem (DFS)</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/54/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/54/</guid><description>Description A ring is compose of n circles as shown in diagram. Put natural number 1, 2, …, n into each circle separately, and the sum of numbers in two adjacent circles should be a prime. Note: the number of first circle should always be 1. Input n (0 Output The output format is shown as sample below. Each row represents a series of circle numbers in the ring</description></item><item><title>HDU 1242 - Rescue（BFS 优先队列）</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/53/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/53/</guid><description>Description Angel was caught by the MOLIGPY! He was put in prison by Moligpy. The prison is described as a N * M (N, M Angel’s friends want to save Angel. Their task is: approach Angel. We assume that “approach Angel” is to get to the position where Angel stays. When</description></item></channel></rss>