<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>二分三分查找 on 淡淡博客 – 记录生活点滴，关注Python数据挖掘、深度学习相关技术</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/tags/%E4%BA%8C%E5%88%86%E4%B8%89%E5%88%86%E6%9F%A5%E6%89%BE/</link><description>Recent content in 二分三分查找 on 淡淡博客 – 记录生活点滴，关注Python数据挖掘、深度学习相关技术</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.i-ll.cc/tags/%E4%BA%8C%E5%88%86%E4%B8%89%E5%88%86%E6%9F%A5%E6%89%BE/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HDU 3714 - Error Curves (三分查找)</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/66/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/66/</guid><description>Description Josephina is a clever girl and addicted to Machine Learning recently. She pays much attention to a method called Linear Discriminant Analysis, which has many interesting properties. In order to test the algorithm’s efficiency, she collects many datasets. What’s more, each data is divided into two parts: training data and test data. She gets</description></item><item><title>POJ 1905 - Expanding Rods(二分查找)</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/65/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/65/</guid><description>Description When a thin rod of length L is heated n degrees, it expands to a new length L’=(1+n*C)*L, where C is the coefficient of heat expansion. When a thin rod is mounted on two solid walls and then heated, it expands and takes the shape of a circular segment, the original rod being the chord of the</description></item><item><title>POJ 1064 - Cable master(二分)</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/71/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/71/</guid><description>Description Inhabitants of the Wonderland have decided to hold a regional programming contest. The Judging Committee has volunteered and has promised to organize the most honest contest ever. It was decided to connect computers for the contestants using a “star” topology - i.e. connect them all to a single central hub. To organize a truly honest contest, the Head of the Judging Committee has decreed</description></item><item><title>POJ 2456 - Aggressive cows(二分)</title><link>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/70/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.i-ll.cc/archives/70/</guid><description>Description Farmer John has built a new long barn, with N (2 His C (2 Input Line 1: Two space-separated integers: N and C Lines 2..N+1: Line i+1 contains an integer stall location, xi Output Line 1: One integer: the largest minimum distance Sample Input 5 3 1 2 8 4 9 Sample Output 3 Hint OUTPUT DETAILS: FJ can put his 3 cows in the stalls at positions 1,</description></item></channel></rss>