<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>贪心算法 on 淡淡博客</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/tags/%E8%B4%AA%E5%BF%83%E7%AE%97%E6%B3%95/</link><description>Recent content in 贪心算法 on 淡淡博客</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blogg.i-ll.cc/tags/%E8%B4%AA%E5%BF%83%E7%AE%97%E6%B3%95/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HDU 1009 - FatMouse' Trade（贪心）</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/56/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/56/</guid><description>Description FatMouse prepared M pounds of cat food, ready to trade with the cats guarding the warehouse containing his favorite food, JavaBean. The warehouse has N rooms. The i-th room contains Jii pounds of JavaBeans and requires Fii pounds of cat food. FatMouse does not have to trade for all the JavaBeans in the room, instead, he may get Jii* a% pounds of JavaBeans if he pays Fii* a% pounds</description></item><item><title>POJ 2431 - Expedition (贪心 优先队列)</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/57/</guid><description>Description A group of cows grabbed a truck and ventured on an expedition deep into the jungle. Being rather poor drivers, the cows unfortunately managed to run over a rock and puncture the truck’s fuel tank. The truck now leaks one unit of fuel every unit of distance it travels. To repair the truck, the cows need to drive to the nearest town (no</description></item><item><title>POJ 3069 - Saruman's Army(贪心)</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/58/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/58/</guid><description>Description Saruman the White must lead his army along a straight path from Isengard to Helm’s Deep. To keep track of his forces, Saruman distributes seeing stones, known as palantirs, among the troops. Each palantir has a maximum effective range of R units, and must be carried by some troop in the army (i.e., palantirs are not allowed to “free f</description></item><item><title>Code Forces 587A - Duff and Weight Lifting（贪心）</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/60/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/60/</guid><description>Description Recently, Duff has been practicing weight lifting. As a hard practice, Malek gave her a task. He gave her a sequence of weights. Weight of i-th of them is 2wi pounds. In each step, Duff can lift some of the remaining weights and throw them away. She does this until there’s no more weight left. Malek asked her to minimize the number of</description></item><item><title>Code Forces 588A - Duff and Meat（贪心）</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/59/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/59/</guid><description>Description Duff is addicted to meat! Malek wants to keep her happy for n days. In order to be happy in i-th day, she needs to eat exactly ai kilograms of meat. There is a big shop uptown and Malek wants to buy meat for her from there. In i-th day, they sell meat for pi dollars per kilogram. Malek knows all numbers a1, …, an and p1, …</description></item><item><title>Codeforces 581C - Developing Skills(贪心)</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/61/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/61/</guid><description>Description Petya loves computer games. Finally a game that he’s been waiting for so long came out! The main character of this game has n different skills, each of which is characterized by an integer ai from 0 to 100. The higher the number ai is, the higher is the i-th skill of the character. The total rating of the character is calculated as the sum of</description></item><item><title>HDU 2037 - 今年暑假不AC(贪心)</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/67/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/67/</guid><description>Description 今年暑假不AC？” “是的。” “那你干什么呢？” “看世界杯呀，笨蛋！” “@#$%^&amp;amp;*%…” 确实如此，世界杯来了，球迷的节日也来了，</description></item><item><title>HDU 2021 - 发工资咯：） (贪心)</title><link>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/68/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogg.i-ll.cc/archives/68/</guid><description>Description 作为杭电的老师，最盼望的日子就是每月的8号了，因为这一天是发工资的日子，养家糊口就靠它了，呵呵 但是对于学校财务处的工作人员来说，这一天则是</description></item></channel></rss>